Architecture Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- 20th Century Architecture (Box 41)
  - Holland (Box 53)
    - Architects (Box 53)
      - Berlage, H.P. [Slide boxes 318-319] (Box 53–54)
      - Doesburg, Theo van [Slide box 319] (Box 54)
      - Klerk, Michel de (Box 54)
      - Koolhas, Rem (Box 54)
      - Oud J., J.P. (Box 54)
    - Cities (Box 54)
      - Aalsmeer (Box 54)
      - Amsterdam (Box 54)
        - Banks (Box 54)
          - Stock Exchange [Slide boxes 319-320] (Box 54)
        - Housing [Slide box 320] (Box 54)
          - Amster South (Box 54)
          - Dageraad (Box 54)
          - Drie Hoven (Box 54)
          - Mercatorplein (Box 54)
          - Public Utility (Box 54)
          - Student Dorm (Box 54)
        - Museums (Box 54)
        - Office Buildings (Box 54)
        - Schools (Box 54)
          - Open Air (Box 54)
          - Orphanage [Slide boxes 320-321] (Box 54)
      - Apeldoorn [Slide box 321] (Box 54)
      - Bergen (Box 54)
      - Bussum (Box 54)
      - Delft (Box 54)
      - Groningen (Box 54)
      - The Hague (Box 54)
      - Hilversum (Box 54)
      - Huis-ter-Heide (Box 54)
      - Nagele (Box 54)
      - Noord Wijkerhout (Box 54)
      - Rotterdam [Slide box 322] (Box 54)
        - Banks (Box 54)
        - Housing (Box 54)
        - Industrial Buildings (Box 54)
        - Stores (Box 54)
      - Scheveningen (Box 54)
      - Utrecht (Box 54)
        - Schroeder House (Box 54)
  - Hong Kong (Box 54)
    - Miscellaneous [Slide boxes 322-323] (Box 54)
  - Hungary (Box 54)
    [Slide box 323]
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 54)
  - India (Box 54)
    - Ahmedabad (Box 54)
    - Ajmer (Box 54)
    - Belapur (Box 54)
    - Bhopal (Box 54)
    - Bombay [Slide boxes 323-324] (Box 54)
    - Calcutta [Slide box 324] (Box 54)
      - Government Buildings (Box 54)
      - Houses (Box 54)
    - Chandigarh (Box 54)
      - Plans (Box 54)
      - Assembly (Parliament) (Box 54)
      - High Court Building [Slide box 325] (Box 54)
      - Secretariat (Box 54)
    - Chopda Taluka (Box 54)
    - Indore (Box 54)
    - Jaipur (Box 54)
    - Madras (Box 54)
    - New Delhi (Box 54)
      - Government Buildings (Box 54)
        - US Embassy [Slide box 326] (Box 54)
        - Viceroy's House (Box 54)
          - Plans and Sections (Box 54)
          - Exterior (Box 54)
          - Interior (Box 54)
          - Gardens (Box 54)
    - Serampore (Box 54)
  - Indonesia (Box 54)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 54)
  - Iraq (Box 54)
    - Miscellaneous Cities [Slide boxes 326-327] (Box 54)
  - Iran (Box 54)
    [Slide box 327]
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 54)
  - Israel (Box 54)
    - Kibbutz (Box 54)
    - Cities (Box 54)
      - Jerusalem (Box 54)
      - Haifa [Slide box 328] (Box 54)
      - Renovot (Box 54)
      - Tel Aviv (Box 54)
  - Italy (Box 54)
    - General (Box 54)
    - Landscapes (Box 54)
    - Architects (Box 54)
      - Albini, Franco (Box 54)
      - Baldessari, Luciano (Box 54)
      - Brasini, Armando (Box 54)
      - Chiattone, Mario (Box 54)
      - De Giorgio (Box 54)
      - Gruppo "La Burbera" (Box 54)
      - Libera, Adalberto (Box 54)
      - Limongelli, Alessandro (Box 54)
      - Mazzoni, Angiolo (Box 54)
      - Moretti, Luigi (Box 54)
      - Natalini, Adolfo (Box 54)
      - Nizzoli, Marcello (Box 54)
      - Pagano, Giuseppe [Slide box 329] (Box 54)
      - Ponti, Gio (Box 54)
      - Portaluppi, Piero (Box 55)
      - Rossi, Aldo (Box 55)
        - City Hall, Muggio (Box 55)
        - Hotel on Grand Canal, Venice (Box 55)
        - Monument to the Resistance (Box 55)
        - Students' Resistance, Chieti (Box 55)
        - Theater for Genoa (Box 55)
        - Teatro Del Mundo, Venice (Box 55)
      - Sabbatine, Innocenzio (Box 55)
      - Sant'elia, Antonio [Slide boxes 329-330] (Box 55)
      - Sartosi, A. [Slide box 330] (Box 55)
      - Sottsass, Ettore (Box 55)
      - Superstudio (Box 55)
      - Terragni, Giuseppe (Box 55)
    - Cities (Box 55)
      - Alessandria (Box 55)
      - Amalfi (Box 55)
      - Ancona (Box 55)
      - Avezzano (Box 55)
      - Asolo (Box 55)
      - Boca (Box 55)
      - Bologna [Slide box 331] (Box 56)
      - Bolzano (Box 56)
      - Brescia (Box 56)
      - Broni (Box 56)
      - Busto Arsizio (Box 56)
      - Capri (Box 56)
      - Carrara (Box 56)
      - Cervinia (Box 56)
      - Ciampino (Box 56)
      - Cittadello Vigodarzeri (Box 56)
      - Como (Box 56)
        - Caso Del Fascio (Fascist Party Headquarters) (Box 56)
        - Novocomum Apartments (Box 56)
        - Monument to War Dead (Box 56)
        - Sant'Elia Kindergarten (Box 56)
      - Cortina d'Ampezzo (Box 56)
      - Diano Marina (Box 56)
      - Fagnano Olona (Box 56)
      - Florence [Slide box 332] (Box 56)
        - General Views (Box 56)
          - Air Views (Box 56)
          - Scoppio (Box 56)
          - Flood, 1966 (Box 56)
          - Streets [Slide box 333] (Box 56)
        - Churches (Box 56)
        - Houses- Apartments (Box 56)
        - Squares (Box 56)
      - Genoa (Box 56)
      - Ghisalba (Box 56)
      - Giussano (Box 56)
      - Gubbio (Box 56)
      - Lastra a Signa (Box 56)
      - Livorno (Box 56)
      - Marcellise (Box 56)
      - Milan (Box 56)
        - Galleria V. Emanuele (Box 56)
        - Churches (Box 56)
        - Expositions (Box 56)
        - Gates [Slide box 334] (Box 56)
        - Houses (Box 56)
        - Houses- Apartments (Box 56)
        - Monuments (Box 56)
        - Office Buildings (Box 56)
        - Palaces (Box 56)
        - Squares (Box 56)
        - Stations (Box 56)
      - Modena (Box 56)
      - Monte Cassino (Box 56)
      - Montecchio (Box 56)
      - Montepulciano (Box 56)
      - Monza (Box 56)
      - Mozzo (Box 56)
      - Naples (Box 56)
      - Novara (Box 56)
      - Padua (Box 56)
      - Palermo [Slide box 335] (Box 56)
      - Pegognaga (Box 56)
      - Pescia (Box 56)
      - Positano (Box 56)
      - Possagno (Box 56)
      - Ravello (Box 56)
      - Redipuglia (Box 56)
      - Riola (Box 56)
      - Rome (Box 56)
        - Plans (Box 56)
        - Planning (Box 56)
          - Mussolini Plan (Box 56)
          - Via Della Conciliazione (Box 56)
        - General Views [Slide boxes 335-336] (Box 56)
        - Air Views [Slide box 336] (Box 56)
        - Streets (Box 56)
        - Churches (Box 56)
          - Church of the Jubilee (Box 56)
        - Exhibitions (Box 56)
          - Anniversary, Fascist Revolution, 1932 [Slide box 336-337] (Box 56–57)
          - E.U.R, 1942 [Slide box 337] (Box 57)
        - Government Buildings (Box 57)
        - Houses- Apartments (Box 57)
        - Housing (Box 57)
        - Industrial Buildings (Box 57)
        - Monuments (Box 57)
        - Mosques (Box 57)
        - Schools (Box 57)
        - Squares (Box 57)
          - Foro Italico [Slide box 338] (Box 57)
            - Foro Italico Stadium (Box 57)
          - Forum Mussolini (Box 57)
        - Stadiums (Box 57)
          - Palazzette dello Sport (Box 57)
        - Stations (Box 57)
        - Stores (Box 57)
        - Vatican (Box 57)
        - Villas (Box 57)
      - Sabaudia (Box 57)
      - San Marino (Box 57)
      - Sauze d'Oulx (Box 57)
      - Schio (Box 57)
      - Siena [Slide box 339] (Box 57)
        - Palio (Box 57)
      - Tavole (Box 57)
      - Terni (Box 57)
      - Tivoli (Box 57)
      - Trieste (Box 57)
      - Turin (Box 57)
        - Plans (Box 57)
        - Gneral Views (Box 57)
        - Churches (Box 57)
        - Exhibitions (Box 57)
        - Squares (Box 57)
      - Urbino (Box 57)
      - Venice [Slide box 340] (Box 57)
        - Plans and Maps (Box 57)
        - General Views (Box 57)
        - Exhibitions (Box 57)
          - Biennale 1980 (Box 57)
        - Museums [Slide box 341] (Box 57)
        - Theaters (Box 57)
      - Verona (Box 57)
      - Viareggio (Box 57)
      - Vietri-sul-Mare (Box 57)
  - Jordan (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 57)
  - Kuwait (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 57)
  - Lebanon (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 57)
  - Malaysia (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 57)
  - Malta (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 57)
  - Norway (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 57)
  - Pakistan (Box 57)
    - Islamabad (Box 57)
    - Karachi (Box 57)
  - Poland (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous Cities [Slide boxes 341-342] (Box 57)
  - Portugal (Box 57)
    [Slide box 342]
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 57)
  - Rumania (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 57)
  - Russia (Box 57)
    - General (Box 57)
    - Architects (Box 57)
      - Cernihov, Jakov (Box 57)
      - Leonidov, Ivan (Box 57)
      - Lissitzky, El [Slide boxes 342-343] (Box 57–58)
      - Vesnin, Alexande [Slide box 343] (Box 58)
    - Cities (Box 58)
      - Kharkov (Box 58)
      - Kiev (Box 58)
      - Leningrad (Box 58)
        - Decorations of Streets, Squares (Box 58)
        - Churches (Box 58)
        - Government Buildings (Box 58)
          - Admiralty (Box 58)
        - Houses-Apartments (Box 58)
        - Museums (Box 58)
        - Schools [Slide box 344] (Box 58)
        - Squares (Box 58)
        - Theaters (Box 58)
      - Moscow (Box 58)
        - Clubs (Box 58)
        - Churches (Box 58)
        - Government Buildings (Box 58)
        - Houses-Apartments (Box 58)
        - Houses-Residential (Box 58)
          - Melnikov House (Box 58)
        - Museums (Box 58)
        - Squares (Box 58)
      - Rostov (Box 58)
      - Tsarkoe Selo (Box 58)
  - Saudi Arabia (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 58)
  - Singapore (Box 58)
    [Slide box 345]
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 58)
  - South Africa (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 58)
  - Spain (Box 58)
    - Landscape (Box 58)
    - Architects (Box 58)
      - Bofill, Ricardo (Box 58)
      - Casas, Manuel de las (Box 58)
      - Gaudi, Antonio (Box 58)
      - Pena Ganchegui, Luis (Box 58)
    - Known Locations (Box 58)
      - Alcala Del Rio (Box 58)
      - Argentona (Box 58)
      - Astorga (Box 58)
      - Barcelona (Box 58)
        - Bridges (Box 58)
        - Churches (Box 58)
          - Church of the Colonia Guell [Slide boxes 345-346] (Box 58)
          - Sagrada Familia (Holy Family) [Slide box 346] (Box 58)
            - Models and Sections (Box 58)
            - East Exterior View (Box 58)
            - West Interior View (Box 58)
            - Exterior Sculpture (Box 58)
            - Pinnacles (Box 58)
            - West Towers (new construction) (Box 58)
        - Estates (Box 58)
          - Finca Guell (Box 58)
        - Exhibitions (Box 58)
          - German Pavilion, 1929 [Slide box 347] (Box 58)
          - Restaurant Del Parque della Ciutadella, 1888 (Box 58)
        - Hospitals (Box 58)
        - Houses-Residential (Box 58)
          - Casa Batllo (Box 58)
            - Exterior [Slide box 348] (Box 58)
            - Interior (Box 58)
            - Rooftops (Box 58)
          - Casa Calvet (Box 58)
          - Casa Guell (Box 58)
          - Casa Mila (Box 58)
            - Exterior (Box 58)
            - Interior [Slide boxes 348-349] (Box 58–59)
            - Rooftop [Slide box 349] (Box 59)
          - Casa Vicens (Box 59)
        - Housing (Box 59)
        - Markets (Box 59)
        - Office Buildings (Box 59)
          - La Fabbrica (Box 59)
        - Parks (Box 59)
          - Parque Guell (Box 59)
            - Doric Colonnade (Box 59)
            - Galleries and Viaducts (Box 59)
            - Gatehouses (Box 59)
            - Serpentine terrace (Box 59)
        - Restaurants [Slide box 350] (Box 59)
        - Schools (Box 59)
          - Colegio Teresiano (Box 59)
        - Squares (Box 59)
        - Theaters (Box 59)
        - Villas (Box 59)
      - Bilbao (Box 59)
      - Brai (Box 59)
      - Comille (Box 59)
      - Calpe, Alicante [Slide box 351] (Box 59)
      - Fuenterrabia (Box 59)
      - Garraf (Box 59)
      - Gerona (Box 59)
      - Granada (Box 59)
      - Jerez de la Frontera (Box 59)
      - La Manzanera (Box 59)
      - Madrid (Box 59)
      - Mataro (Box 59)
      - Merida (Box 59)
      - Palma de Mallorca (Box 59)
      - Pamplona (Box 59)
      - Puente la Reina Navarra (Box 59)
      - Reus (Box 59)
      - Sallent (Box 59)
      - San Sebastian (Box 59)
      - Sant Cugat del Valles (Box 59)
      - Santander (Box 59)
      - Seville (Box 59)
      - Tarragona (Box 59)
      - Toledo (Box 59)
      - Valencia (Box 59)
      - Valle de los Caidos (Box 59)
      - Vilafrance (Box 59)
  - Sweden (Box 59)
    [Slide box 352]
    - Alberga (Box 59)
    - Djursholm (Box 59)
    - Fors (Box 59)
    - Goteborg (Box 59)
    - Klippan (Box 59)
    - Linkoping (Box 59)
    - Malmo (Box 59)
    - Solvesborg (Box 59)
    - Stennas (Box 59)
    - Stockholm (Box 59)
      - Cemetaries (Box 59)
        - Woodland Chapel (Box 59)
        - Woodland Crematorium (Box 59)
      - Government Buildings (Box 59)
      - Libraries (Box 59)
      - Schools (Box 59)
      - Theaters (Box 59)
  - Switzerland (Box 59)
    [Slide boxes 352-353]
    - Basel [Slide box 353] (Box 59)
    - Berne (Box 59)
      - Houses-Apartments (Box 59)
    - Bettlach (Box 59)
    - Bottmingen (Box 59)
    - Cadenazzo (Box 59)
    - Davos (Box 59)
    - Dornach (Box 59)
      - Gotheanum (Box 59)
        - Boiler House (Box 59)
        - Duldeck House (Box 59)
        - Haus de Jaager [Slide box 354] (Box 59)
        - Stained Glass (Box 59)
    - Freibourg (Box 59)
    - Geneva (Box 59)
    - La Chaux-de-Fonds (Box 59)
      - Scala (Box 59)
      - Houses (Box 59)
        - Villa Cornu (Box 59)
        - Villa Fallet (Box 59)
        - Villa Jacquemet (Box 59)
        - Villa Schwob (Box 59)
        - Villa Stotzer (Box 59)
    - Lac Laman (Box 59)
    - Lausanne (Box 59)
    - Le Locle (Box 59)
    - Ligornetto (Box 59)
    - Ligrigano (Box 59)
    - Lucerne (Box 59)
    - Lugano (Box 59)
    - Massagno [Slide box 355] (Box 60)
    - Montreux (Box 60)
    - Morbio Superiore (Box 60)
    - Morcote (Box 60)
    - Origlio (Box 60)
    - Schaffhausen (Box 60)
    - Stabio (Box 60)
    - Vignanello (Box 60)
    - Zurich (Box 60)
      - Heidi Weber Pavilion (Box 60)
      - Technical University (Box 60)
  - Taiwan (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 60)
  - Thailand (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 60)
  - Tunisia (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 60)
  - Turkey (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 60)
  - Yugoslavia (Box 60)
    [Slide box 356]
    - Mestrovic, Ivan (Box 60)
    - Belgrade (Box 60)
    - Cavtat (Box 60)
    - Dubrovnik (Box 60)
    - Ljubljana (Box 60)
    - Sarajevo (Box 60)
    - Split (Box 60)
    - Zagreb (Box 60)
  - Latin America (Box 60)
    - Argentina (Box 60)
      - Miscellaneous Architects (Box 60)
      - Cities (Box 60)
        - Buenos Aires (Box 60)
          - General (Box 60)
          - Planning (Box 60)
          - Plans [Slide boxes 356-357] (Box 60)
          - Views [Slide box 357] (Box 60)
          - Banks (Box 60)
          - Churches (Box 60)
          - Fortifications (Box 60)
          - Government Buildings (Box 60)
          - Harbors and Docks (Box 60)
          - Hospitals (Box 60)
          - Houses- Apartments (Box 60)
          - Librairies (Box 60)
          - Museums (Box 60)
          - Office Buildings (Box 60)
          - Squares (Box 60)
            - Plaza de Mayo (Box 60)
        - Catamarca (Box 60)
        - Concepcion Del Uruguay (Box 60)
        - Cordoba (Box 60)
        - Mar del Plata (Box 60)
        - Martinez (Box 60)
        - Parana (Box 60)
        - Santa Fe (Box 60)
        - Santa Rosa (Box 60)
    - Bolivia (Box 60)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 60)
    - Brazil (Box 60)
      - Architects (Box 60)
        - Burle, Marx Roberto [Slide box 358] (Box 60)
        - Niemeyer, Oscar (Box 60)
      - Cities (Box 60)
        - Brasilia (Box 60)
          - General (Box 60)
            - Views (Box 60)
          - Churches (Box 60)
            - Cathedral (Box 60)
          - Government Buildings (Box 60)
            - Administrative Building (Box 60)
            - Judiciary Building (Box 60)
            - Ministry Buildings (Box 60)
            - Triangle of the Powers (Box 60)
          - Hotels (Box 60)
          - Housing (Box 60)
            - Residential Superblocks (Box 60)
          - Palaces (Box 60)
            - Palace of Alvorada (Box 60)
          - Roads (Box 60)
          - Theaters (Box 60)
            - Ouro Preto [Slide boxes 358-359] (Box 60)
            - Palmeira dos Indios [Slide box 359] (Box 60)
            - Pampulha (Box 60)
            - Petropolis (Box 60)
        - Rio de Janeiro (Box 60)
          - Banks (Box 60)
          - Expositions (Box 60)
          - Government Buildings (Box 60)
          - Houses- Apartments (Box 60)
          - Houses (Box 60)
          - Museums [Slide box 360] (Box 60)
          - Office Buildings (Box 60)
          - Palaces (Box 60)
          - Theaters (Box 60)
        - Salvador (Box 60)
        - Sao Paolo (Box 60)
    - Chile (Box 60)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 60)
    - Guatemala (Box 60)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 60)
    - Mexico (Box 60)
      - Barra de Navidad (Box 60)
      - Celaya (Box 60)
      - Hermosillo (Box 60)
      - Merida (Box 60)
      - Mexico City (Box 60)
        - Churches (Box 60)
          - Chapel of S. Vincent de Paul (Box 60)
          - Espirito Santo (Box 60)
          - Nuestra Senora de Loreto (Box 60)
          - Virgin of the Miraculous Medal [Slide boxes 360-361] (Box 60–61)
        - Gardens [Slide box 361] (Box 61)
        - Government Buildings (Box 61)
        - Houses (Box 61)
          - Los Clubes section (Box 61)
          - Pedregal section (Box 61)
        - Housing (Box 61)
        - Industrial Buildings (Box 61)
        - Monuments (Box 61)
        - Museums (Box 61)
        - Office Buildings [Slide box 362] (Box 61)
          - Communications Building (Box 61)
          - Cedulas Hipotecarias (Box 61)
          - Compania de Seguros Monterrey (Box 61)
          - Seguros la Libertad (Box 61)
        - Schools (Box 61)
          - University of Mexico (Box 61)
            - Administration Building (Box 61)
            - Library (Box 61)
            - Medical School (Box 61)
            - Science Building [Slide boxes 363] (Box 61)
            - Stadium (Box 61)
            - Swimming Pool (Box 61)
        - Squares (Box 61)
        - Theaters (Box 61)
          - Palace of Fine Arts (Box 61)
      - Monterrey (Box 61)
      - Puebla (Box 61)
      - Queretaro (Box 61)
      - S. Luis Potosi (Box 61)
      - Tlalpan (Box 61)
      - Xochimilco (Box 61)
    - Paraguay (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 61)
    - Puerto Rico (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 61)
    - Uruguay (Box 61)
      - Montevideo (Box 61)
    - Venezuela (Box 61)
      - Caracas (Box 61)
        - Schools (Box 61)
  - Caribbean (Box 61)
    [Slide box 364]
    - Barbados (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 61)
    - Cuba (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 61)
    - Jamaica (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 61)
    - S. Vincent (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 61)
    - Trinidad (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 61)
  - North America (Box 61)
    - Bermuda (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 61)
    - Canada (Box 61)
      - Montreal (Box 61)
        - Expositions (Box 61)
          - Expo '67 (Box 61)
            - German Pavilion (Box 61)
            - U.S. Pavilion (Box 61)
        - Houses (Box 61)
          - Bronfman House [Slide boxes 364-365] (Box 61)
        - Houses- Apartments [Slide box 365] (Box 61)
          - Habitat (Box 61)
    - New Maryland (Box 61)
    - Ottawa (Box 61)
    - S. Stephen (Box 61)
    - Toronto (Box 61)
    - Waterloo, Ontario (Box 61)
  - United States (Box 61)
    - General (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 61)
      - Cartoons (Box 61)
      - Mayan Revival (Box 61)
      - Pop Architecture (Box 61)
      - Shaker (Box 61)
    - Barns (Box 61)
    - Dams [Slide box 366] (Box 61)
    - Diners (Box 61)
    - Early Settlements (Box 61)
    - Grain Elevators (Box 61)
    - Highways/Streets (Box 61)
    - Houses (Box 61)
      - Various (Box 61)
      - Plans/Elevations [Slide box 367] (Box 62)
    - Housing (Box 62)
      - Various (Box 62)
      - Baltimore (Box 62)
      - Bay St. Louis (Box 62)
      - Beaumont, TX (Box 62)
      - Chicago (Box 62)
      - Dallas, TX (Box 62)
      - Goldsboro, NC (Box 62)
      - Greenwich, CT (Box 62)
      - Hagerstown, MD (Box 62)
      - McAllen, TX (Box 62)
      - New York (Box 62)
      - Orlando, FL (Box 62)
      - Richmond, VA (Box 62)
    - Industrial Buildings (Box 62)
    - Interiors [Slide boxes 367-368] (Box 62)
      Xx for painted rooms (murals) see Painting U.S.- Porter, Rufus
      Xx for paintings of Interior rooms, see Painting U.S. –Emory, Ella and Leavitt, and Joseph Warren
    - Interiors: Exhibits [Slide box 368] (Box 62)
    - Interiors: Museum Rooms (Box 62)
      - Various (Box 62)
      - American Museum, Bath, England (Box 62)
      - Bayou Bend Collection, Houston, Texas (Box 62)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 62)
      - Museum of City of New York (Box 62)
        - Stettheimer Doll House (Box 62)
      - Winterthur Museum [Slide boxes 368-369] (Box 62)
    - Mobile Homes [Slide box 369] (Box 62)
    - Parks (Box 62)
    - Schools (Box 62)
    - Stores (Box 62)
      - Various (Box 62)
      - Best Products (Box 62)
    - Architects (Box 62)
      - Miscellaneous [Slide boxes 369-370] (Box 62)
      - Abraham, Raimund, 1935- [Slide box 370] (Box 62)
      - Allied Works Architecture (Box 62)
      - Arquitectonica (Box 62)
      - Austin, Henry, 1804-1891 (Box 62)
      - Beeby, Thomas, 1941- (Box 62)
      - Cret, Paul P., 1876-1945 (Box 62)
      - De Bretteville, Hodgetts & Kupper (Box 62)
      - Davis, Alexander Jackson, 1803-1892 (Box 62)
      - Deamer, Peggy (Box 62)
      - Diller & Scofidio (Box 62)
      - Downing, Andrew Jackson, 1815-1852 (Box 62)
      - Drummon, William E., 1876-1946 (Box 62)
      - Eisenman, Peter [Slide boxes 370-371] (Box 62)
      - Eyre, Wilson, 1858-1944 [Slide box 371] (Box 62)
      - Ferriss, Hugh, 1889-1962 (Box 62)
      - Fuller, Buckminster, 1895-1983 (Box 62)
        - Various (Box 62)
        - Dymaxion Bathroom (Box 62)
        - Dymaxion Bathroom (Box 62)
        - 4D House (Box 62)
      - Furness, Frank, 1839-1912 (Box 62)
      - Gehry, Frank Owen, 1929- (Box 62)
      - Giurgola, Romaldo, 1920- (Box 62)
      - Goff, Bruce Alonzo, 1904-1982 [Slide box 372] (Box 62)
      - Goodhue, Bertram, 1869-1924 (Box 62)
      - Graves, Michael, 1934- (Box 62)
        - Various (Box 62)
        - Aspen, CO, Vacation House (Box 62)
        - FT. Wayne IN, Crooks House (Box 62)
        - Loveladies, NJ, Beach House (Box 62)
        - Vassar College, Art History Building (Box 62)
      - Greenberg, Allan, 1938- (Box 62)
      - Griffin, Marion Mahony, 1871-1962 (Box 62)
      - Griffin, Walter Burley, 1876-1937 (Box 62)
      - Hejduk, John Quentin, 1929-2000 (Box 62)
      - Hood, Raymond M., 1881-1984 [Slide box 373] (Box 63)
      - Jefferson, Thomas, 1743-1826 (Box 63)
      - Johansen, John McLane, 1916- (Box 63)
      - Johnson, Philip Cortelyou, 1906-2005 (Box 63)
      - Kahn, Louis I., 1901-1974 (Box 63)
      - Lafaver, Minard, 1798-1854 (Box 63)
      - Latrobe, Benjamin Henry, 1764-1820 (Box 63)
      - Libeskind, Daniel, 1946- (Box 63)
      - Lin, Maya Ying (Box 63)
        Xx Sculpture U.S.A
      - McKim, Mead & White (Box 63)
      - Moore, Charles, 1925-1993 (Box 63)
        - Various [Slide box 374] (Box 63)
        - Goodman House (Box 63)
        - Otus House Project (Box 63)
        - Resort Hotel Project (Box 63)
      - Nowicki, Matthew, 1910-1950 (Box 63)
      - Pederson & Tilney (Box 63)
      - Pelli, Cesar, 1926- (Box 63)